Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Miller, Mrs. Frank W., 1971
  - Miller, Frederick A., 1940
  - Miller, G. Macculloch, II, 1959
  - Miller, Gail, 1953
  - Miller, Herbert C., 1949-1969
  - Miller, Isabelle, 1939-1945
  - Miller, Mr. and Mrs. J. Don, 1941-1944
  - Miller, John David, 1950-1971
  - Miller, Leonard D., 1952
  - Miller, Lois Mattox, 1941, 1951
  - Miller, Ruth Weir, 1964-1967
  - Miller, Spencer, Jr., 1949
  - Miller, Sydney R., 1939
  - Miller, T. Grier, 1946-1969
  - Miller, William, 1962
  - Mills, Cretyl, 1964-1966
  - Mills, Ira J., 1952
  - Mills, Wilbur, 1969
  - Milzer, Albert, 1952
  - Minerva Pediatrica, 1970
  - Ming, Charles, 1952-1953
  - Minkowski, A., 1953
  - Minnick, David Scott, 1962
  - Minshaw, Jerney J., 1961
  - Mirenda, Catherine, 1960-1961
  - Mirick, George S., 1951-1962
  - Mishkin, Mark M., 1971
  - Missirliu, Constatin, 1956
  - Mitchell, A. Graeme, 1935-1941, 1968
  - Mitchell, Catherine J., 1950
  - Mitchell, F. Thomas, 1952
  - Mitchell, John McK, 1947-1969
  - Mitchell, R.G., 1952
  - Mitchell, Robert B., 1968
  - Mitchell, Walter L., 1950
  - Moat, Albert G., 1961
  - Modern Medicine, 1946-1966
  - Moed, George, 1957
  - Mofenson, Howard C., 1963
  - Mogabgab, William, 1963
  - Mohler, Isabelle B., 1941
  - Molinaro, Leo, 1964
  - Molitch, Matthew, 1957
  - Mollison, P.L., 1955
  - Moloney, P.J., 1963
  - Moncrieff, Sir Alan, 1950-1969
  - Moncrieff, Lady Mary, 1969
  - Monk, J.P., 1962
  - Monk, Paul J., 1952-1953
  - Monroe, Robert W., 1950, 1969-1970
  - Monsma, John Clover, 1961
  - Monson, Carlos M., 1954
  - Montalvo, Jose R., 1959-1963
  - Montgomery, DeWitt H., 1952
  - Montgomery, Frank, 1955
  - Montgomery, George, 1953
  - Montgomery, Horace B., 1952, 1962
  - Moon, E.R., 1940
  - Moon, Virgil H., 1949-1951
  - Moorcraft, Minnie, 1940
  - Moore, Edward F., 1959
  - Moore, Hugh, 1957
  - Moore, J.E., 1950-1953
  - Moore, John C., 1969
  - Moore, Joseph J., 1953
  - Moore, Michael, 1960-1961
  - Moore, Norman S., 1954
  - Moore, Paul J., 1966
  - Moore, Sally, 1958
  - Moore, William J., 1955
  - Moore, William L., 1956
  - Morelli, Lorenzo, 1959-1962
  - Moreschi, Patricia, 1959
  - Morgan, Charlotte H., 1943
  - Morgan, Hugh J., 1953
  - Morgan, Reed A., 1953-1962
  - Morgan, William L., 1951-1952
  - Morgan, William R., Jr., 1943
  - Moriarty, Andrew J., 1960-1967
  - Morison, Robert, 1964
  - Morley, Felix, 1940
  - Morris, Alvan, 1958
  - Morris, C.C., 1954
  - Morris, C.C., II, 1949
  - Morris, Janet, 1943-1945
  - Morris, Paul, 1941-1942, 1952
  - Morrison, Lester M., 1958
  - Morrone, Michele, 1961
  - Morrow, A.L., 1941
  - Morrow, Grant, III, 1959-1961
  - Morselander, Timothy, 1961
  - Morton, Allan R., 1952
  - Morton, Harry E., 1959
  - C.V. Mosby Company, 1941, 1962
  - Moseley, John, 1957
  - Mosher, Thomas E., 1949
  - Mosley, James W., 1950-1971
  - Moss, N. Henry, 1969
  - Mossadegh, M., 1956
  - Mote, John R., 1954
  - Motsay, D.S., 1951
  - Mozziconacci, Pierre, 1956
  - Muckle, Craig W., 1951
  - Mudd, Emily, 1966
  - Mudd, Stuart P., 2.0 folders
  - Mudge, Gilbert H., 1962
  - Mueller, Harry L., 1952
  - Muhlenberg, J. Peter, 1954-1961
  - Muldoon, Robert L., 1959
  - Mullally, Daniel I., 1969
  - Mullen, Nancy, 1961
  - Muncil, Kathy M., 1952
  - Mundo, Fey Del, 1956, 1965
  - Munson, Helen W., 1940-1941
  - Munson, Henry G., 1941
  - Murdock, Thomas P., 1952
  - Murlin, John R., 1942
  - Murlott, Calder C., Jr., 1966-1967
  - Murphy, Douglas, 1962
  - Murphy, Elizabeth A., 1940
  - Murphy, Franklin D., 1952, 1955
  - Murphy, George E., 1944
  - Murphy, John J., 1967-1968
  - Murphy, M. Lois, 1950-1962
  - Murphy, Robert, Jr., 1961
  - Murphy, Robert C., 1965
  - Murray, Donald S., 1964
  - Murray, M.J., 1966
  - Murray, Roderick, 1962, 1966
  - Murto, Robert E., 1956
  - Musser, J.H., 1942
  - Musser, William L., 1951
  - Mustard, Jane, 1954-1962
  - Mycock, Albert, 1960-1962
  - Myer, Barbara, 1961
  - Myers, Ann Jody, 1962
  - Myers, Janice, 1960-1961
  - Nachod, Grace R., 1949
  - Naeye, Richard L., 1967
  - Naficy, K., 1960
  - Naiman, J. Lawrence, 1965-1966
  - Najjar, Victor A., 1949-1956
  - Nancarrow, John F., 1965
  - Nash, F.W., 1960
  - National Broadcasting Company, 1947
  - National Drug Company, 1951, 1961
  - National Health Insurance, 1949
  - Naughton, David, 1961
  - Navarro, Juan E., 1954
  - Naylor, Edward, 1941
  - NEA Service, 1942
  - Nealon, Thomas F., Jr., 1963
  - Needleman, Herbert L., 1954-1966
  - Needleman, Samuel W., 1966
  - Neefe, John R., 1941-1967; 3.0 folders
  - Negro and property values, Undated
    Illinois Commission on Human Relations
  - Neiderman, Sharon, 1961
  - Nelson, Dewey A., 1962
  - Nelson, John M., 1964
  - Nelson, L.F., 1945
  - Nelson, Lawrence M., 1953
  - Nelson, Paul L., 1956
  - Nelson, Russell A., 1967
  - Thomas Nelson and Sons, 1943-1949
  - Nelson, Waldo E., 1940-1971; 5.0 folders
    Contains works by Stokes, chapters for the section on pathogenesis of virus infections, for the publication Textbook in Pediatrics.
  - Nemir, Paul, Jr., 1964-1965
  - Nemir, Rosa Lee, 1946
  - Nesse, G.M., 1952
  - Nester, Nancy, 1961
  - Neter, Erwin, 1951-1952
  - Neth, Robert L., 1966
  - Netrasiri, Arun, 1958
  - New England Journal of Medicine, 1953-1971; 3.0 folders
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1948
  - New York Times, 1953-1957, 1969
  - Newberger, A.C., 1967
  - Newbold, Clement B., 1952-1957
  - Newman, Harris, 1949
  - Newman, Schuyler, 1961
  - Newman, W.R. Elton, 1958
  - Newns, George H., 1959
  - Newsweek, 1940
  - Newton, W.A., Jr., 1951, 1956
  - Nicholls, Edith E., 1950
  - Nichols, Joe D., 1957
  - Nichols, Myron M., 1949-1958
  - Nichols, Robert, 1959
  - Nicholas, Stanley, 1946
  - Nichols, Warren W., 1956-1966
  - Nicholson, J.T.L., 1952
  - Nicholson, Jesse T., 1946-1962
  - Nicholson, John, 1940, 1946
  - Nicholson, John M.W., 1969-1970
  - Nicholson, Mrs. John W., 1944
  - Nicholson, Margaret M., 1942
  - Nicholson, Morris J., 1960
  - Nicholson, Rebecca, 1940-1943
  - Nicholson, Robert, 1963, 1969
  - Nicols, Kathryn S., 1962
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1952
  - Niedelman, Ruth, 1941
  - Niehaus, Robert W., 1954-1955
  - Nierenberg, R.T., 1950
  - Nishiyama, Hiroshi, 1961
  - Nitobe, Uncle Inago, Undated
  - Nitschmann, H., 1954-1956
  - Nixdorf, George, 1940
  - Nixon, Norman, 1949-1955
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1959-1971
  - Noda, Lafayette, 1944
  - Noe, William L., Jr., 1939, 1958-1961
  - Noel, John Vaveseur, 1953-1954
  - Nolan, Edgar V., 1953
  - Nolting, Wilfred S., 1948-1949
  - Noone, Ernest L., 1941-1964; 2.0 folders
  - Norcross, B.M., 1948
  - Nordgren, Carl W., 1950
  - Norman, Archibald P., 1956-1962
  - Norman, John C., 1969
  - Norris, Marjorie, 1948
  - Norris, Robert F., 1940, 1956
  - Norris, William A., 1955
  - North Carolina Medical Journal, 1947
  - North, Francis, 1949
  - Norton, J.W., 1966-1967
  - Notkin, Herbert, 1957
  - Novorro, E., 1956
  - Nowell, Peter C., 1970
  - Noyes, Dorothy, 1958-1959
  - Nungester, W.J., 1949
  - Nurses Official Directory, 1938
  - Nute, William L., Jr., 1946
  - Oakley, Cletus, 1964, 1969
  - Oakley, David R., 1967
  - Oakwood School, 1949
  - Obermayer, Herman J., 1950
  - Obermayer, Leon J., 1950-1970
  - O'Brien, Henry R., 1948
  - Ocheltru, Eleanor, 1940
  - O'Conner, Ruth, 1964
  - O'Connor, Basil, 1961
  - O'Donnell, Francis T., 1940, 1949
  - O'Donnell, George J., 1953
  - O'Donovan, Charles, 1941
  - Oettinger, Leon, Jr., 1945-1962
  - Offner, Frances L., 1955
  - O'Flynn, Nora, 1951
  - O'Halloran, Alice M., 1943
  - O'Keefe, Pierce, Undated
  - Okuda, Rukuro, 1961
  - Oldfelt, Vera, 1950-1951
  - Oliner, Mrs. B.G., 1954-1955
  - Oliphant, Audrey B., 1952
  - Olitsky, Peter, 1940
  - Olmstead, Richard W., 1965
  - Olmsted, J.G.M., 1946
  - Olney, R.C., 1963
  - Olshin, Irving J., 1958-1963
  - Olstad, Robert B., 1957
  - Omans, Walter B., 1965-1966
  - O'Meara, Patrick M., 1965
  - Oncley, J.L., 1946
  - O'Neil, Gerald C., 1940-1947
  - Onori, Mary Ellen, 1961
  - Opie, Eugene L., 1971
  - Oppenheim, Richard, 1961
  - Oppenheimer, Albert, 1957
  - Oravsky, Ernest, 1954, 1961
  - Ordway, Nelson K., 1952-1962
  - Orentreich, Norman, 1965
  - Ornduff, William W., 1947
  - Orr, James M., 1954-1960
  - Orr, William J., 1942-1953
  - Orsini, A., 1955
  - Orson, Jay M., 1959-1960
  - Orteza, Josefina M., 1960
  - Ortlieb, Rene J., 1968
  - Osborn, Gladstone R., 1956
  - Oski, Frank, 1960
  - Osterlig, Wilbur A., 1952
  - Ostrander, Alveretta, 1953
  - Ostyn, Patricia, 1962
  - O'Sullivan, Ward D., 1960
  - Oswald, G. June, 1961, 1970-1971
  - Overman, William F., 1941
  - Overton, Frank, 1940
  - Owen, Donna, 1968
  - Owen, Hubley, 1944-1945
  - Owen, William G., 1967
  - Oxford University Press, 1942-1943
  - Ozge, Ayse H., 1958
  - Ozyazici, Ayten, 1957
  - Pace, Frank, Jr., 1955
  - Pagano, Joseph S., 1960-1968
  - Page, Edward C., 1945
  - Page, Robert G., 1951
  - Pahl, David, 1961
  - Palladino, Robert, 1961
  - Paller, Mary, 1948
  - Palmer, Harold D., 1941
  - Palmer, John W., 1961-1962
  - Palmer, Walter D., 1958-1959
  - Palmieri, Frank, 1961
  - Pan American Airways Company, 1940-1941
  - Panico, Frederick G., 1947-1948
  - Panos, Theo C., 1949
  - Papenheimer, A.M., Jr., 1956
  - Paradise, Jack L., 1951
  - Parboosingh, Ivan S., 1954
  - Parfentjev, I.A., 1952
  - Parikh, C.K., 1961-1964
  - Park, Edwards A., 1950-1968; 3.0 folders
  - Parkard, Francis R., 1931
  - Parke, Davis and Company, 1948-1949, 1961-1962
  - Parker, Douglas Dodds, 1950
  - Parker, Frank, 1941
  - Parker, Ralph, 1968
  - Parker, Thomas, 1952
  - Parker, William S., 1952
  - Parkhurst, Leonard W., 1965
  - Parkinson, William N., 1940, 1945
  - Parran, Thomas, 1943-1949
  - Parrish, Louis, 1956
  - Parrott, Robert H., 1958, 1966
  - Parsons, Willard H., 1959
  - Parton, George, 1951
  - Pascucci, Joseph D., 1964
  - Pascucci, Stephen E., 1951-1956
  - Pasquariello, Mae Agnes, 1967
  - Pasquariello, P.S., Jr., 1963
  - Pasteur, Louis, Undated
  - Pate, Alice C., 1942-1949, 1969
  - Pate, John R., 1953
  - Pate, Maurice, 1956
  - Patel, Saroj T., 1956-1957
  - Paterson, Donald, 1948-1964
  - Paterson, Thomas G., 1969
  - Pathway School, 1961
  - Patient Care, 1969
    Journal
  - Patierno, Robert, 1967
  - Patrono, Mildred, 1961
  - Patten, Deon, 1956
  - Patterson, Donald, 1956
  - Patterson, E.B., 1959
  - Patterson, Elizabeth Fox, 1948-1949, 1960-1961
  - Patterson, H.M., 1947
  - Patterson, Hubert, 1960
  - Patterson, Joseph H., 1962
  - Patterson, Paul R., 1950, 1957
  - Patterson, Reese, 1966
  - Patton, Paul B., 1955
  - Patton, William Hugh, Jr., 1947-1957
  - Paucker, Elli, 1963
  - Paul, John R., 1939-1971; 5.0 folders
  - Paul, Leita, 1971
  - Paul, Raphael N., 1946-1947
  - Pauling, Linus, 1958-1963
  - Paxson, Chauncey G., 1946-1972
  - Paxson, Newlin F., 1941, 1961
  - Payne, Anthony M.M., 1963, 1968
  - Payne, Franklin L., 1941-1955
  - Payne, Mary Anne, 1952, 1967
  - Peacher, Georgiana M., 1959-1961
  - Peacock, Peter B., 1968
  - Peard, Nancy, 1941
  - Pearlman, Lyon N., 1940-1952
  - Pearson, H.E., 1950
  - Pease Laboratories, 1941
  - Pechter, Bonnie, 1961
  - Peck, Dorothea R., 1946
  - Peczenik, Alois, 1957-1958
  - Pediatric Herald, 1960
  - Pediatric Ophthalmology, 1960-1961
  - Pediatric Research, 1970-1971
  - Peery, Thomas M., 1963
  - Peiser, Kurt, 1951-1952
  - Pemberton, Henry R., 1962
  - Pendergrass, Eugene P., 1941-1970
  - Penfield, Wilder, 1963-1969
  - Penn Mutual Life Insurance, 1959
  - Pennell, Robert B., 1961-1968
  - Penneys, Raymond, 1969-1970
  - Pennoyer, Doris S., 1963
  - Pennsylvania Comprehensive Mental Health Plan, 1964
  - Pennsylvania State Refresher Course, 1947-1949
  - Pepinsky, Abe, 1943
  - Pepinsky, Rae B., 1944-1945
  - Pepper, D. Sergeant, 1969
  - Pepper, Dickinson S., 1942
  - Pepper, Oliver Hazard Perry, 1942-1945
  - Pequet, Arche R., 1961
  - Perera, George A., 1954-1971
  - Perez, Adrian, 1945-1946
  - Perkins, Benjamin S., 1947
  - Perkins, Frank T., 1968
  - Perkins, Warren G., 1944
  - Perkins, William Harvey, 1963
  - Perlingiero, Josephine, 1943, 1945
  - Perlingiero, Nina, 1946
  - Perlman, Eli, 1954
  - Perlman, H. Harris, 1943-1944
  - Perloe, Sidney, 1968
  - Perri, Angelo M., 1944, 1952
  - Perrige, John, 1966
  - Perrott, George St. J., 1958
  - Perry, Henry, 1941
  - Perry, J.W., 1955
  - Perry, John, 1950-1952
  - Perry, Lester H., 1941
  - Perry, Mary Elizabeth, 1939-1947
  - Perry, Seymour, 1966
  - Persons, Robert W., Jr., 1957
  - Peters, John P., 1950-1956
  - Petersen, Howard Charles, 1965
  - Peterson, J.C., 1953-1969
  - Peterson, Patricia, 1961
  - Petrides, Efthimios, 1947
  - Petty, D.J., 1951-1952
  - Peustow, Karver L., 1949
  - Pew, Joseph N., Jr., 1939, 1945
  - Pew, Thomas A., 1960
  - Pewterbaugh, David C., 1940-1941, 1957
  - Pezzati, Pietro, 1961-1962
  - Pfeiffer, Jean Z., 1962
  - Pfeiffer, Mildred C.J., 1944
  - Charles Pfizer and Company, 1952
  - Pfund, Harry W., 1953
  - Phalen, Dale, 1971
  - Pharmacia Laboratories, 1952-1953
  - Pharmacopeia of the U.S.A., 1953
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, 1958-1959
  - Philadelphia Medicine, 1948-1958
  - Philadelphia Private Schools Physicians, 1941
  - Philadelphia School of Occupational Therapy, 1953, 1957
  - Philadelphia Suburban Water Company, 1951
  - Philadelphia Transportation Company, 1954
  - Phillips, Alfred J., 1958
  - Phillips, C. Hayden, 1941-1942
  - Phillips, Charles, 1961
  - Phillips, Robert N., 1956
  - Phillips, T.L., 1959
  - Phillips, Walter M., 1950-1963
  - Phillips, William, 1960-1961
  - Phillips, William A., 1963
  - Phinney, James D., 1945
  - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1952
  - Phoenixville Lead Poisoning, 1948
  - Pickering, Donald E., 1963
  - Pickering, Sir George W., 1967
  - Pickett, Clarence E., 1961
  - Pickles, William N., 1948-1949
  - Piel, Carolyn F., 1952-1958
  - Piel, Gerard, 1963-1969
  - Piel, John J., 1949-1961
  - Piersol, George Morris, 1942-1956
  - Pigott, Albert W., 1941
  - Pike, Robert M., 1948-1949
  - Pilling, George P., IV, 1943-1947
  - Pillsbury, Donald M., 1940-1965
  - Pillsbury, Dorothy, 1942
  - Pindar, Fred, 1946
  - Pinto, A. Pithon, 1942-1943
  - Pinto, Rosemary, 1949-1959
  - Pittman, Margaret, 1971
  - Pitts, Mrs. Henry S., 1939
  - Place, Virgil A., 1961
  - Platou, Ralph V., 1945-1961
  - Platt, Charles, Jr., 1940, 1946
  - Platt, Dorothy, 1966
  - Platt, Ruth, 1954
  - Platt, Yungman and Company, 1954-1960
  - Plotkin, Stanley A., 1957-1967; 2.0 folders
  - Plotnikoff, N.P., 1966
  - Plum, Fred, 1968
  - Plummer, Harold B., 1953
  - Plummer, James C., 1971
  - Plummer, Norman, 1945
  - Plummer, William, III, 1950-1959
  - Pocono Lake Preserve, 1932-1956; 3.0 folders
  - Poesponegoro, Soedjono D., 1956-1958
  - Poey Seng Hin, 1957-1972
  - Poggioli, Renato, 1960
  - Pohl, John F., 1945
  - Polacheck, Larry, 1960
  - Poley, Irvin C., 1951, 1964
  - Poley, Ruth, 1968
  - Polgar, George, 1957-1963
  - Polk, Charles Robeson, 1942
  - Polk, D. Stewart, 1941, 1961-1965
  - Polk, Lewis D., 1956, 1969
  - Pollack, Jerome, 1968-1969
  - Pollack, Philip, 1956
  - Poncher, Henry G., 1945-1951
  - Pongsupath, Soncha, 1955-1956
  - Pope, Carita, 1940
  - Popper, Hans, 1952-1953, 1960
  - Porta, Eduardo, 1971
  - Porter, Joseph E., 1952-1953
  - Porter Matthews Company, 1945
  - Porter, Philip J., 1957-1958
  - Positions available for physicians, 1958-1959
  - Post, Joseph, 1951
  - Postgraduate medicine, 1950
  - Potamkin, Alan and Robert, 1952-1957
  - Potamkin, Victor H., 1950, 1956
  - Potkonski, Leopold A., 1964
  - Potter, Ellen C., 1940-1941
  - Potter, H. Phelps, Jr., 1965
  - Potter, John P., 1966
  - Potter School, 1942
  - Potts, Asa Wing, 1940-1950
  - Potts, Florence W., 1942
  - Powell, Barbara, 1962
  - Powell, John H., 1955
  - Powers, Grover F., 1943-1962
  - Powers, Hugh, 1939-1946
  - Powers, Lee, 1952
  - Powis, Ethel M., 1941
  - Prader, Andrea, 1961-1962
  - Pradera, Emilio Soto, 1953
  - Prall, Grace, 1940
  - Pratt, Edward L., 1956-1967, undated; 2.0 folders
  - Prentiss, Mary Eleanor, 1948, 1960-1966
  - Press, Anne, 1969
  - Preston, Edmond, III, 1949-1971
  - Price, Alice, 1958
  - Price, Anne H., 1958
  - Price, Edmund T., 1942
  - Price, F. E., 1947
  - Price, Harrie B., 1971
  - Price, John S., 1966-1967
  - Price, Martha, 1968
  - Price, Pamela Ann, 1968
  - Price, Philip, 1972
  - Price, Sarah, 1963-1964
  - Prickitt, Elwood J., 1965
  - Prier, James E., 1966
  - Primakow, Carole, 1962
  - Prince, Alfred M., 1963
  - Prince, George E., 1950-1951
  - Pringle, Duncan McColl, 1941-1943, 1966-1967
  - W.F. Prior Company, Inc., 1945
  - Propst, Charles, 1953
  - Prosser, M.W., 1948
  - Provident Trust Company, 1945-1947, 1956-1958
  - Prugh, Dane G., 1945, 1951
  - Pruitt, William R., 1950-1954, 1971
  - Pryor, Helen B., 1941
  - Public Health Nursing, 1940
  - Public Health Nursing Service, 1948
    Delaware County
  - Publicity, 1952-1953, 1962
  - Puck, Theodore T., 1964
  - Puerto Rico, 1956
  - Pugh, Delbert L., 1962-1963
  - Pullen, Derra, 1961
  - Pulone, Benedetto, 1961
  - Pulrang, Peter C., 1961
  - Puntenny, Irving, 1961
  - Purdie, Arnold, 1968
  - Purshottam, N., 1947-1949
  - Puschett, Jules B., 1969
  - Putnam, Henry M., 1941-1951
  - Putnam, Tracy J., 1941
  - Quaker Oats Company, 1948
  - Quaker Service--Vietnam, 1969
  - Qualls, Gene T., 1955, 1957
  - Quarles, Mrs. Emmet A., 1948, 1957
  - Quarterly Review of Pediatrics, 1946
  - Quiaoit, Narcisa L., 1961
  - Quillian, Warren W., 1942, 1960
  - Quinn, Norman J., 1952-1956
  - Rabe, Edward F., 1951
  - Rabinovitz, Saul, 1941
  - Radbill, Samuel X., 1941-1968
  - Radfux, Elisabeth, 1962
  - Raffel, Sherry, 1950-1961
  - Raffensberger, Edward C., 1952-1954
  - Ragazzo, Beth Ann, 1961
  - Raiford, Morgan B., 1946
  - Rainbow, Kathryn A., 1950-1951
  - Rainey, Froelich, 1967
  - Rainey, Willard G., 1941
  - Rains, Claude, 1961
  - Raju, V. Balagopal, 1955
  - Rake, Geoffrey W., 1942-1955
  - Ralston, Edgar L., 1963
  - Rambo, Mrs. Scheidt, 1960
  - Rammelkamp, Charles H., 1951, 1955
  - Randall, Alexander, IV, 1946-1954, 1971
  - Randall, Perlingiero J., 1947-1969
  - Randall, Peter, 1956-1964
  - Randall, W.S., Jr., 1952-1953
  - Rankhorn, Dorothy S., 1966
  - Ransmeier, John C., 1948
  - Rao, B. Gopalakrishna, 1968-1971
  - Rapoport, Milton, 1945-1964
  - Rappaport, Judy, 1959
  - Rappaport, Stanley, 1942-1944
  - Rappleye, Willard, 1947
  - Rasberry, E.A., Jr., 1957-1959
  - Rashkind, William Jacobson, 1957-1962
  - Rather, L.J., 1956-1957
  - Ratner, Bret, 1948
  - Ratnoff, Oscar D., 1961
  - Rattew, Philip L., 1948
  - Rausen, Aaron R., 1954
  - Rautmann, H., 1952
  - Rautmann, Margund, 1949-1953
  - Ravdin, Elizabeth, 1951-1952
  - Ravdin, Isidore S., 1939-1966; 2.0 folders
  - Ravenholt, R.T., 1970
  - Rawlinson, Helen L., 1955-1962
  - Rawnsley, Howard M., 1965
  - Rawson, Arthur J., 1939
  - Ray, David B., Jr., 1967
  - Rayburn, Samuel, 1959-1960
  - Raycraft, Margaret Mary, 1961
  - Rayne, Denman, Undated
  - Read, Frances E.M., 1944-1962
  - Read, Hilton S., 1955-1966
  - Read, W.T., 1948
  - Reader's Digest, 1948
  - Reagan, Elspeth M., 1955
  - Reardon, Joseph P., 1960
  - Reath, George, 1956
  - Reck, Lawrence E., 1940-1964
  - Record Room, 1947
  - Rectanus, Daniel R., 1954-1961
  - Rector, Mardeen, 1961
  - Redewill, F.H., 1952
  - Redmond, Anthony P., 1959
  - Redpath, Frederick L., 1966
  - Redpath, Robert Upjohn, Jr., 1943-1969
  - Reed, Lola S., 1947-1958
  - Reed, Wellford C., 1952
  - Reeves, Helene M., 1952
  - Reeves, Robert P.T., 1952
  - Reeves, Rufus S., 1942
  - Reeves, Steve, 1963
  - Regan, Diane, 1963
  - Regan, Judith, 1961
  - Regules, Pedro, 1959-1960
  - Reich, Zvi, 1965
  - Reichardt, Pamela, 1961
  - Reichelderfer, Thomas E., 1962
  - Reid, David H.S., 1958-1963
  - Reid, Dorothy E., 1958
  - Reid, J.D., 1957
  - Reid, Legh W., 1945-1947
  - Reidpath, Robert, Undated
  - Reilly, C.A., 1962
  - Reilly, Charles M., 1964-1971
  - Reilly, James J., 1947-1958
  - Reilly, William A., 1940-1963
  - Reimann, Hobart A., 1940, 1963
  - Reimann, Stanley P., 1949
  - Reinhart, Harry A., 1961-1965
  - Reinhold, John G., 1949-1952
  - Reisinger, John A., 1949
  - Reisinger, Paul B., 1959
  - Reisman, Henry A., 1949
  - Reiss, E. Edward, Jr., 1950
  - Remington Rand, Inc., 1948, 1952
  - Renard, Suzanne G., 1945-1946
  - Renthal, A. Gerald, 1970
  - Reprint Requests, 1939-1957; 2.0 folders
  - Retting, Mary Ann, 1966
  - Rexroad, Althea, 1957
  - Reyersbail, Gertrude, 1942
  - Reyniers, James A., 1952
  - Reynolds, Emma Michael, 1941
  - Reynolds, Frank Russell, 1949-1952
  - Reynolds, Levi E., 1964
  - Reynolds, Mildred Davis, 1947
  - Reynolds, William R., 1964-1965
  - Rhoads, C.P., 1950
  - Rhoads, Charles J., 1951
  - Rhoads, Donald V., 1949
  - Rhoads, Elizabeth, 1967
  - Rhoads, Esther B., 1957
  - Rhoads, George, 1965-1968
  - Rhoads, J. Edgar, 1957
  - Rhoads, Jonathan E., 1945-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Rhoads, Robert M., 1965-1966
  - Rhodes, A.J., 1953
  - Rhodes, E. Washington, 1948
  - Rhodes, Katerina, 1951-1952
  - Rhodes, P., 1958
  - Rice, Brian, 1961-1962
  - Rice, R. Gerald, 1958, 1962
  - Rich, Homer R., 1948
  - Rich, John, 1949
  - Rich, John F., 1946
  - John F. Rich Company, 1955-1956
  - Richards, A.N., 1945-1959
  - Richards, Dickinson W., 1964
  - Richards, Lillian W., 1966
  - Richards, Richard Peter, 1954-1961
  - Richardson, Francis L., 1949-1955
  - Richardson, Frederick, 1961
  - Richie, David S., 1964
  - Richmond, Julius B., 1961-1963
  - Richter, Curt P., 1959-1969
  - Ricketts, Henry T., 1970
  - Ricks, James Hoge, 1948
  - Ridgway, William H., 1940-1941
  - Riggs, Donald T., 1945
  - Rigler, David, 1955-1957
  - Riley, Francis A., 1950
  - Riley, Harold M., 1967-1969
  - Riley, Harris D., Jr, 1957-1966
  - Riley, Richard L., 1940-1967
  - Riley, William G., 1948
  - Ringold, Mrs. Herbert H., 1963
  - Rink, John C., 1944
  - Rioppelle, Arthur J., 1961
  - Rippel, Mrs. George S., 1954
  - Ripy, Howard, 1947-1948
  - Risley, Brenda, 1961
  - Rittenberg, Benjamin B., 1948-1970
  - Rittenhouse Book Store, 1963
  - Ritter, Joseph A., 1941-1959
  - Rivers, Thomas, 1946-1954; 2.0 folders
  - Rivinus, F. Markoe, 1967-1970
  - RN: National Magazine for Nurses, 1962
  - Robb, Gertrude Graham, Undated
  - Robbins, Frederick C., 1952-1967
  - Robbins, J.G., 1947
  - Robbins, J. Stanton, 1936
  - Roberson, William Gibbs, 1952
  - Roberts, A. Addison, 1969
  - Roberts, Arthur S., 1964
  - Roberts, Brooke, 1951-1971
  - Roberts, H. Radclyffe, 1961
  - Roberts, Jay, 1971
  - Roberts, Kingsley, 1946
  - Roberts, M. Hines, 1954-1955
  - Roberts, William H., 1946
  - Robertson, Alexander Farish, Jr., 1956-1957
  - Robertson, Elizabeth Chant, 1939
  - Robertson, Harold F., 1949, 1956
  - Robertson, Henry C., Jr., 1950
  - Robertson, James, 1952, 1956
  - Robertson, O.H., 1945-1958
  - Robertson, Roy R., 1947
  - Robins, Eli, 1960-1962
  - Robinson, B.F., 1965
  - Robinson, Geoffrey C., 1966
  - Robinson, Isabelle S., 1965
  - Robinson, J. Franklin, 1965
  - Robinson, James W., 1963
  - Robinson, John, 1965
  - Robinson, Miles H., 1940-1958
  - Roby, Ross, 1946, 1948
  - Rocha, Jose Martinho da, 1960
  - Roche, Philip Q., 1940, 1948
  - Roche, Robert P., 1967
  - Rock, John, 1962
  - Rockefeller, David, 1970
  - Rockefeller Institute, 1959
  - Roddis, Eugenia C., 1944
  - Roddy, Rudolf L., 1940-1948
  - Rodman, Walter L., 1961
  - Roe, Daphne Anderson, 1955-1956
  - Roebling, Mary G., 1947, 1967
  - Rogers, Arthur M., 1955
  - Rogers, David E., 1952
  - Rogers, Fred B., 1957
  - Rogers, George M., 1968
  - Rogers, Joel A., 1964
  - Rogers, Max, 1964
  - Rogerson, Alexander G., 1949-1952
  - Rohl, D., 1967-1972
  - Rola, Americo, 1949
  - Roll, Fred, 1961
  - Rollings, Harry E., 1947
  - Romano, Nicholas R., 1957
  - Romano, Vincent E., 1948
  - Rome, Walter J., 1953